Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org
[gentle music playing]
[chickens clucking]
I don't know if that's true…
Oh.
God dammit.
Richard's guys must have tore
a hole in the coop.
I'm gonna…
Okay, honey. Honey, listen.
Just sit down, have your coffee,
and… I'll take care of the chickens.
We should've just sold to that developer.
Do you really mean that?
[machinery whirring]
[sighs]
You know what's killing me?
Is that Will's still working with Richard.
Even after he threatened to cut us out.
Maybe he thinks it'll keep him in check.
Why? Nothing else does.
[sighs]
I'm done with this.
I'm not gonna let Richard or anybody else
make decisions about our property.
I'm gonna fix it.
How?
I have an idea.
I don't want to talk about it now,
because it's kind of going,
but if it works,
it will sort all this out.
Okay? So just… just give me a couple days.
Okay.
I'm gonna go look for
some wire in the garage.
-Okay.
-[clucking]
I'm just gonna sit here
and have some coffee.
With my chicken.
[whistle blowing on video]
[footsteps approaching]
You watching the University of Texas game?
Yeah, they run this combo
of a zone and man-to-man defense.
It's gorgeous.
Thinking of using it for the Bighorns?
Um, actually, I got a meeting
with the UT rep at the college thing.
First time they've come out here,
and I kind of wanna
get in their coaching program.
I've been trying
to get a feel for their playbook,
how they run their offense,
how they run their defense, and just…
I'm boring you, aren't I?
No. No, it's just, uh…
I'm really glad
my little brother's got his mojo back.
Please. You're 20 minutes older than me.
Okay?
Yeah, and every minute counts, kiddo.
Stop.
We should go get ready.
We got time.
I cannot be late.
I have to help set up
all the college fair booths.
If it doesn't go smoothly, I won't be able
to focus on our final mock driver's test.
Okay. Okay, we'll go.
[Jackie] Thank you.
What?
Nothing.
I… I just…
I love you.
[upbeat, inspirational music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
[Dylan] What you doing?
Uh, I'm developing my own video game.
Just working on some designs.
Wow, that's pretty amazing. You know that?
[chuckles] Yeah, whatever.
What do you want?
Well, I did just wanna hang out with you,
but now I also want to see your drawings.
No, absolutely not.
Come on.
Fine.
You get one quick look.
[Dylan] Wow.
It's kind of like that, um, new
Quantum Justice movie that just came out,
except a little more fantasy stuff.
-You've seen it?
-No. No, I've just read all the books.
-What's this guy's name?
-I'm still workshopping him.
He's, like, probably not even gonna be
in the game, so…
Too bad. He's my favorite.
Shouldn't you be doing something else?
Like, uh, prepping to talk
to the Oklahoma rep tomorrow?
Actually, uh, my dad and I
already met with him.
What? How'd it go?
[clears throat] Uh,
really well.
Like, my dad was… happy.
[Kiley] Hmm.
He said he was proud of me.
Well, you should celebrate.
You know, now that you mention it,
I think I would like to celebrate
by going to see Quantum Justice.
Wanna come with?
Seriously?
Yeah, you're not working tonight, right?
You're right. I am not.
Great. Well, I will see you
at the Mirror Ball at 7:00.
Dylan?
Is this, like, a date?
What? No way.
Oh no, right, sorry, I…
Kiley, Kiley, Kiley, I'm joking.
[chuckles]
Do you want it to be?
No. [chuckles]
I don't know.
All right, well, maybe we can decide
after the movie?
Deal.
[Jackie] So,
the last two colleges confirmed.
Let's see, and you marked all
the classrooms for the one-on-ones, right?
We have a lot of students coming.
We don't want anyone to get lost.
-Yeah, no one's gonna miss them.
-Perfect.
Okay, and that's the end of my checklist.
-So what's wrong? Did we miss something?
-No.
-It's not a big deal.
-Is it 'cause there's no Princeton rep?
No, Miss Jacobs said
they'd come next year.
Is it the driver's test?
I've actually been doing okay
in driver's ed.
All I've got to do now is get through
my final mock test,
and I'll be ready for the real one.
-Okay, fine.
-Wha…
-It's Alex.
-Oh, I knew it! Okay, what's wrong?
He said he loved me.
-Well, didn't he already tell you that?
-It was different this time.
I think he means it,
and I think he expects me to say it back.
Well, you do like him, don't you?
Yeah, of course, obviously.
Well, I don't know what the problem is.
I mean, I say I love you to everyone.
Like, all the time.
You, Skylar, the lunch lady
that one time we had Oreo cheesecake.
It just feels like a big deal after
everything that's happened between us.
Mm, I get that.
Well, it doesn't mean
you'll never get there, right?
Um… right.
I gotta go.
-Guys, the sign's upside down.
-[Grace] Jackie, where are you going?
All right, so we'll start at the, uh…
Let's put a pin in this for now.
I'll get back to you.
[Katherine] Hi.
So you know your guys tore a hole
in our chicken coop this morning?
[sighs] I'm so sorry, Mom.
It won't happen again.
It's this pressure to rush
that's making us a little sloppy.
Well, it's fine now
'cause your dad fixed it.
But that pressure…
that pressure's not coming from us.
Yeah, I know that.
I really don't like
that Richard's pushing you so hard.
It'll be okay. It's just…
I have to figure out
how to get him to listen to me.
-I thought you were working together.
-Yeah, me too.
Sorry. I gotta get back.
Okay, so right now we have
all of these colleges confirmed.
[Skylar] Okay, nice.
That's a good list.
-In 15-minute intervals--
-[Skylar] Are there anymore…
-Jackie?
-Yeah.
-Hi.
-Oh, so…
-Uncle Richard, this is Grace.
And you remember Skylar?
Yeah, it's nice seeing you again.
I was just stopping by
to pick up something to go,
but since you're here, you wanna
grab some dessert from the Lark?
Sorry, we've really got to get ready
for this college fair tomorrow.
Another time.
For sure.
It was nice seeing you both.
-You too.
-Yeah.
Okay.
-[grace laughs]
-Georgetown?
-Focus. Focus. Focus.
-Anyways…
-[Skylar] Grace! You're getting mean.
-[Grace] Didn't say anything! You said it.
His Girl Friday or It Happened One Night.
Oh, It Happened One Night, obviously.
The Walls of Jericho scene.
Me and my grandma used to watch it
every year for her birthday.
It was her favorite movie.
Clark Gable's performance
is just perfection.
You know, now that we've got
our SATs back and everything,
we should practice our monologues.
Yeah, I can help you.
I'd help with yours too.
We could maybe think
of a scene to do together.
Or maybe we could even
coordinate our applications.
-Danny.
-Yeah?
I'm not applying to Tisch.
Okay. Yeah, that's cool.
We… we don't have to go to the same place.
Juilliard is tough,
but after that summer program--
I'm gonna go to community college
here in Silver Falls.
Oh.
Yeah, that way I can avoid
getting into crazy debt
and maybe transfer to a four-year
after a couple years to major in business.
Yeah, but you… you love acting.
-You shouldn't give it up.
-I'm not giving up.
I've been thinking about this
since middle school. I have a plan.
Okay, but plans can change,
and you'd be an amazing actor.
I did one play.
In high school.
Did I enjoy it?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna be an actor.
Like you said, you did one play,
and you were great.
Okay, so maybe if you did another one,
you'd realize that is what you want.
I know what I don't want.
A boyfriend who thinks he knows
what I want better than I do.
I'm gonna go home.
Okay, yeah, I'll drive you.
I can walk.
[somber music playing]
Alex, if I wanted to learn
how to play Confederacy of the Gods,
could you help me?
Uh, sure.
Just so you know, it took Kiley
and me over 100 hours just to get ranked.
-I have no idea what that means.
-[Alex] Yeah, exactly.
Why would you even wanna play?
You've never been into video games.
Mm, well, Zach's a big fan.
Zach's a big fan.
Yeah, and apparently
this new expansion pack came out.
-I want to see what he's raving about.
-A new expansion pack came out?
-How did I miss that?
-I mean, do you even play anymore?
Well, you know, I haven't had much time.
Yeah, you're kind of like
a totally different person now.
Zach thinks you're going through a phase.
Whatever. What would he know?
Anyway, at least I'm changing for myself
and not for somebody else.
Oh, I didn't say it like it's a bad thing.
Wait, are you talking about me?
If I'm changing, I feel like it's because
I'm becoming, like, more myself.
Like Zach's helping me be
the best version of myself.
Is he? 'Cause…
it seems like
it's all about what Zach likes,
what Zach thinks, what Zach does,
what Zach wants.
That's not true.
If you're not using your account,
can I have it?
Hell no.
Oh my God, shut up.
-Hi.
-[Zach] Hey, you. Can you talk?
Yeah.
-Oh my God.
-[Nathan] No, I'll just leave. [chuckles]
[sighs] Ay, ay, ay.
Okay, tell me are you a cookie dough bites
or a sour gummy worm kind of gal?
Oh, both. And then some.
You know you're not supposed to bring
your own snacks, right?
I can't afford the snacks here.
Well, this one's on me.
Oh, no, no, that's… that's okay.
Come on. When was the last time
you got treated to something?
Kiley, I'm going
to be buying candy anyway.
I can't remember the last time
I had actual movie theater candy.
Most of my work money goes to Grams.
Don't your parents send her cash
to take care of you?
They've still got the Quantum Justice
themed popcorn buckets.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, we're definitely
getting one of those, right?
Um, hey, uh,
we'll take two cookie dough bites,
some sour gummy worms,
a large Quantum Justice popcorn,
and a soda?
-Yeah.
-Two sodas, please.
[bell rings]
[Zach] Surprise.
Hey.
-Hey.
-[Nathan] Oh, sorry. I…
I gotta get to band practice.
What, now?
I thought you had band fourth period.
Yeah, but we're working on a new set,
so they'll be waiting for me.
Come on, you can skip it.
I wanted to take you to breakfast.
Um…
Yeah, I guess one practice won't hurt.
That's my guy.
You comin'?
Thank you.
Victoria. Hey. George.
Oh, it's so nice
to finally meet you in person.
I know. Yeah, thank you for coming in.
Oh, my pleasure.
Your artisanal cider is
the highlight of my family's fall.
Thank you.
[Victoria] I was happy that your ranch
didn't have to close down last year.
And I'm even happier you're considering us
as your wine supplier
for your new venture.
Well, about that.
I actually wanted to talk to you
about another way we could work together.
I'm listening.
-Can I get you some coffee?
-Sure.
[upbeat music playing]
One for you.
-We're so good at this.
-I know.
Wait a minute.
Oh, did you know they have
a pastry chef from Paris on the faculty?
-France?
-Kentucky. But, you know…
[chuckles] Well, while you go pursue
your patisserie dreams,
I'm set on Georgetown.
They have
a great Indigenous studies working group.
Mm. What about you, Jackie?
Honestly, I'm just glad
things are going well.
[Grace] Fair.
[murmurs]
There weren't supposed to be
any empty booths.
I'll be right back.
You're welcome.
Jackie, hey!
Thank you so much
for helping put all this together.
And your Excel spreadsheets…
a work of genius.
Thanks.
But why are there empty booths?
Did something happen?
Some of the colleges had to pull out.
Scheduling conflicts, people getting sick,
and just now, car trouble.
It happens. Don't take it to heart.
Okay.
I'll need your help letting students know
which reps couldn't make it.
-Great. Thank you. I appreciate that.
-Of course.
Hi. Um, is Pat Harris from UT here?
Cole, I am so sorry, but Mr. Harris's car
broke down on the way here.
Right. Um…
-Yeah. It's… it's okay.
-Cole.
Well, well, uh,
what if, let's just say, someone who's
good at fixing cars could help Mr. Harris?
Maybe even manage to do a one-on-one
about the college while they're there?
Of course, this is all hypothetical.
Obviously, I would never tell
a student to skip school.
Yeah, but I… I came with Danny today,
so I can't go anywhere anyways.
[sighs] Uh… uh…
-Take my car.
-Are you serious?
It's a stick.
You can drive a stick, right?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Okay. Take these before I change my mind.
Be careful with her, Cole.
I will call Pat and tell him
that Silver Fall High's best mechanic
is on his way.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome. Good luck.
[Jackie] Are you okay?
This is your chance to stand out
from all the other applicants.
You have to go.
Okay.
Okay. I guess.
Good luck.
I'm pretty sure the spaces will fill up.
We'll be good.
[gasps] Wait, Sky,
we should try goldsmithing.
Imagine me with my own jewelry line.
What should I call it?
[gasps] "A little bit of Grace."
-Wait, that's actually sickening.
-I know!
-[makes sizzling sound]
-[both laugh]
[pensive music playing]
-[Zach] See you soon.
-Okay.
Should we go somewhere else?
No.
Um… you two go ahead.
I wanna talk to Nathan.
Okay. Well, this is going well though.
[Skylar] Hey.
Hey.
So that looks like it's getting serious.
Yeah.
Who have you managed to interview so far?
Just a few.
Show me.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Look, Nate.
I believe in honesty in relationships.
I think you need to be careful. There are
things you don't know about Zach.
Okay. I'll bite. What things?
Things you should ask him about yourself.
Look, all I'm trying to say is,
no matter how nice things
may feel right now,
don't lose yourself in him.
Uh, Skylar.
Okay, fine.
In the name of honesty,
are you looking out for me
or are you just jealous?
Seems like the jealousy
wasn't totally in my head.
But the Nate I knew
wouldn't act like this.
Well, I don't know what to tell you.
Maybe you didn't know me
as well as you thought you did.
Like I said,
just be careful.
-Okay?
-Okay.
Kiles, did you get my text
about the Confederacy of the Gods
expansion pack?
Uh, yeah. Sorry. Sorry, I was… I was busy.
Oh. Yeah, sure.
Uh, dinner rush
at Monty's is no joke, right?
Actually, I wasn't working. I was out.
Out?
[Kiley] Yeah.
I… I know it's hard to imagine
that I have other things besides work
and video games going on, but I do.
-I know that.
-So what is it then?
You have some girl problem you want
to emotionally vomit all over me?
No, we haven't talked in a while,
and I really wanted to--
Maybe you should ask
one of your rodeo groupies to help you.
I have things to do.
Kiley.
Hey.
Uh, everything okay?
Everything's great.
I'll see you later, Alex.
[somber music playing]
-Um, are… are you sure everything's okay?
-Yeah.
Yeah, absolutely.
And, um, last night… definitely a date.
-Really?
-Really.
Good.
[phone ringing]
-Oh, it's my grandma. I gotta go.
-Well, can I help?
[Kiley] Grams? What is it? Are you okay?
-Thank you.
Okay, bye.
Jackie.
Can't wait for this social interaction.
What's up?
Listen, I don't totally get your whole
pizza voucher PTA things or whatever,
but this event is, um,
actually kind of awesome.
I mean, who knew I had the grades for
University of Wisconsin-Madison, right?
That's great. I'm glad the fair
is opening up some ideas for you.
You know what? You would've made
a better class president than Paige.
I have a feeling this Hawaii trip
she promised is not gonna happen.
-You think?
-[Maria] Look, I gotta go.
I got a one-on-one with Northwestern.
I'll see you later.
[Tara] Look at this turnout.
With all the last-minute sign-ups,
we're completely booked.
You know, I wasn't sure enough juniors
would be interested in today,
but you have proven me wrong.
-It was nothing.
-[Tara] It wasn't nothing.
With your help, we've made these students
feel like they can go anywhere
and be anything.
Um, do you have any more
of those maps printed?
-I think we ran out.
-There's a pile on my desk.
-Great.
-Thank you.
Cole?
What are you still doing here?
Did you forget something?
No.
It's just…
What?
[sighs]
I'm not ready for this.
Come on. You're gonna do fine.
I've never done anything like this, okay?
My… my interview with Tony
for the auto shop was like,
"Hey, I know you like cars.
Come work for me."
Sure, but once you're in it, it's easy.
What if I say something stupid?
You won't.
Come with me.
I wish I could,
but with the college fair--
Please.
I know it's a big ask.
Okay.
Yeah, I can leave things
to Grace and Skylar.
So the meteor falling is actually
a catalyst for four different storylines
before they all converge…
Well, I don't want to spoil it.
[girls chuckle]
I mean, I… I have to read this.
Can I borrow it when you're done?
Yeah, sure.
Cool.
-I'll see you later, Alex.
-[Alex] See ya.
What were you even talking about?
Oh, this new sci-fi series.
-Basically, after this meteor--
-No wonder they looked so bored.
All right.
Where are you going?
Look,
I don't know what's up with you lately,
but if you're gonna be a dick, I'm out.
Alex, wait.
It's Skylar.
Um…
He just, like, gave me
this vague-ass warning about Zach,
and I'm, like, freaking out.
-Maybe he's got a point.
-What? I mean…
Okay, so, like,
I missed one band practice.
-And I wanna do the things he likes, but--
-Hold up.
You missed band practice,
and you're trying to get into video games?
Yeah, but isn't it good to try new things?
Yeah.
As long as you're not giving up things
you like and only doing what he wants.
[scoffs] Okay, I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I should just talk to him,
ask him what Skylar means?
Yeah.
And stop skipping band practice.
♪ Just leave the car in neutral ♪
♪ And meet me after dark ♪
♪ The spot around the corner… ♪
Next question.
How would you describe yourself?
[exhales] Let's see.
Charming, good-looking…
Okay. Good to see
you got your confidence back.
I guess as a fixer, you know?
I look at something, like a car,
see what it needs,
and find a way to fix it.
I just wish life could be so simple.
Good.
Okay, New York.
Show me how it's done.
Where do you see yourself in five years?
Oh, please. That's too easy.
About to graduate Princeton.
Okay, I should've figured.
Yeah. [chuckles]
I think I can do this now.
See? I knew it.
By being prepared,
you can get everything you want.
Everything, huh?
Everybody deserves to dream big,
especially my friends.
Like you.
Right.
-Hi.
-Hey, Grace.
-Hey.
-Have you seen Jackie anywhere?
Yeah, I think
she's still on the road with Cole. Yeah.
With Cole?
Uh, yeah.
I mean, the rep's car broke down.
Um, it's for sure like
a student-teacher thing.
You know, uh, the boring aesthetic
of cardigan sweaters and corduroy.
Okay, I'll just text her then.
Okay.
Yeah.
And I've been assistant coaching
my school's team ever since.
There aren't a lot of high schoolers
who can handle leading their peers.
It's not always easy.
Thank you for, uh, agreeing to do this.
Least I could do. Thanks for your help.
Sure.
Now, uh, I've got another question.
How would your friends describe you?
Um…
I think
that I'm a lot different
from the guy I was a year ago,
in that I don't always get things right.
But when I don't,
I try my best to fix them.
That's great to hear.
We look for more than just perfect grades.
Resilience and determination
can go a long way.
[Jackie] Oh no. Already?
[Cole] And as far as this bad boy goes,
I think she's looking pretty good.
[rep] Okay.
[Cole] Let me just do one more thing,
and then you should be good to go.
-[rep] Thank you.
-[Cole] You got it.
[overlapping chatter]
I know you're not interested
in community college.
No. But I am interested in apologizing
to the girl who wants
to go to community college.
Apologizing for…
Not listening.
I just figured you loved acting
as much as I did.
And it was wrong.
And I totally get why
we aren't together anymore.
Danny, couples fight all the time.
Doesn't mean we're broken up.
Unless… you want to be.
No.
No. No, absolutely not.
[Erin] Good.
Then apology accepted.
Like I said, drama club was fun,
but acting's a long shot.
I feel pretty good about my odds.
I know.
I just… I don't want to see you get hurt.
I just think it's better
to be more realistic.
So I'm unrealistic?
You know that's not what I mean.
You know what is realistic?
Applying to business schools in New York
to see if you could get in.
Applications are expensive.
I told you, I… I can't afford it.
Well, fee waivers exist.
Scholarships exist. You could try.
Danny, I can't make plans
that revolve around you.
I have to do what's best for me.
Like I said, I have a plan.
Yeah, but we could've tried
to plan together.
Instead, you've just completely
shut me out of your future.
I didn't know we had an expiration date,
but apparently we do.
Danny.
-Did you hear that?
-Yeah, it went really well.
I even asked him about my grades.
And he said my coaching experience
could help make up for it.
Just glad to see you so happy.
Whoa, hey. Everything okay?
I'm going to miss
my final mock driving run.
Oh, Jackie, I'm… I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
I'll ask Coach Allen to make it up.
Uh, wait. Wait.
How about a little practice now?
Ha ha, very funny.
I'm serious.
-I've never driven a stick shift before.
-Oh, please.
You'll be fine. I'll… I'll teach you.
I'll teach you. Come on.
Come on.
Do you think this should be
the cover photo?
Come on, we can't use that photo.
I just want everyone
to see you the way that I do.
The hottest, coolest, sweetest guy ever.
Zach, did something happen
between you and Skylar?
Did he say something to you?
Look, just because he didn't give you
the attention you deserved and lost you--
What was it?
Okay.
Okay, yes. Um…
Yeah. Something did happen
between me and Skylar.
My sophomore year.
I hadn't come out yet.
But Skylar and I started hooking up.
But after a while,
he was just always so busy.
I mean, it was always
Student Council or the paper.
I mean, that's why I joined,
so I could get closer to him.
But no matter what I did
to try and get him to focus on me,
he was always busy.
And finally,
he told me that he wanted
to be with somebody who was out.
And so I came out.
Eventually.
But you two were already together.
So wait, are you…
Are you just trying to get back at Skylar,
or are you trying to get back with him?
No.
No, Nathan.
I didn't think the past mattered.
It doesn't matter.
It…
Yeah, it does.
[coach] Is Jackie coming?
I know I don't have to tell you
that there's no texting and driving.
Let's go.
[Alex] She's on her way.
You know, after work,
my hardworking, seven-months-pregnant wife
looks forward to dinner
that I make for her on the table by 6:30.
You mind doing the speed limit, buddy?
I can't do that.
-Excuse me?
-Sorry.
It's just, uh, Jackie's busy
with college fair stuff,
and I know how much
this final run means to her,
so I can't go any faster.
All right. We'll wait
a little longer for her.
Okay. Easy, eyes on the road.
-Okay.
-Perfect.
Now for the highway.
Are you serious?
Yes. You've got this.
Okay.
Just feel the car as you go. Right?
Foot on the clutch.
[tires squeal]
[engine revs]
Take it easy.
Ready to shift.
Good. Now.
[emotional music playing]
A little more gentle.
-You're gonna have to shift again.
-I got it.
[knocking on door]
Come in.
[door opens, closes]
Hi, Katherine.
What you doing here, Richard?
I wanted to talk to you.
I'm sorry about your chicken coop.
Hmm.
Not sorry about cutting George and I
out of decisions or sidelining Will?
We needed to see
a return on the investment quickly
and to speed things up.
The investors need clarity
and decisiveness,
and you know George
has been dragging his feet.
And Will has always been a junior partner,
and he is great. He is.
But he needs direction.
He's never done this before.
I understand
that our financial situation isn't great
and that we have to get this done.
But pushing this through
at the expense of my husband and my son,
that's not gonna fly with me.
You don't get to make that choice
when it's other people's money!
[somber music playing]
How much of your own money
did you invest in this, Richard?
-You don't need to worry about that.
-Well, I am now.
I couldn't convince my business partners
to invest the amount we needed,
so I made up the difference
with my own money.
-I used my apartment as collateral.
-[Katherine groans] Oh.
-I…
-Oh my God.
…figured if I got involved with the ranch,
that I could save Jackie's home
here in Silver Falls too
and spend more time with her.
She's all the family I have left.
And I wanted her to feel settled
and to feel safe.
She doesn't need
any more upheaval in her life.
And I understand that, Richard.
I really do.
You didn't have to take on so much risk.
I mean, we could've found another way.
Could you?
We always have.
Here's what you need to know.
You will always have a place in my home
because you're family now too.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
Can you do me one favor?
-Are you gonna push your luck?
-[sighs]
Let me tell George.
He should hear it from me.
I can do that.
Thanks.
-You're late.
-I know. I'm sorry.
Luckily, Alex had
a very convincing argument on your behalf,
so I'll give you the benefit of the doubt.
Let's get moving.
That was cool of you to get
Coach Allen to stick around for her.
It's nothing.
Meeting go okay?
Yeah.
I think so.
Good.
Skylar?
What do you want?
I wanted to talk to you
about what happened with Nathan.
What is there to talk about?
You stole my boyfriend
just to prove you could.
No, that wasn't it.
Then what is it?
Is it because we broke up?
Are you still upset about that?
Of course I am. I--
We were just in different places, Zach.
It wasn't anything more than that.
We're not in different places anymore.
I'm out. We're both single.
What?
Nathan and I, we're not together anymore.
[scoffs] Are you serious?
You're unbelievable. You know that?
Look, Skylar, I…
I like Nathan and all, but…
Honestly, I just wanted
to get your attention.
Well, you got that.
Sky!
I miss you.
So what are you saying?
I want you back, Sky.
I didn't know you were still up.
I thought everyone was asleep.
They are.
I just wanted to say thank you
for holding off Coach Allen.
Ah, yeah. He wasn't happy about it.
But I knew how much
you wanted to practice.
You're lucky he didn't make you run laps.
Oh, well, he was this close.
I, uh…
I need to apologize.
For what?
I should've told you that I was
skipping school with Cole and I…
Jackie. Do I need to be jealous?
Of course not.
Absolutely not.
Then it's all good.
-Seriously?
-Seriously.
And I should've said it the other day.
But I love you too.
♪ I'll be right here ♪
♪ Till you're steady ♪
♪ When it's heavy ♪
[coach] All right.
Are you taller than me now?
Goodness gracious.
Mm-hmm.
-…a bit rehearsed.
-Coach!
-Cole, hold on a second.
-What's up?
I didn't want to put
any added pressure on you,
but, uh, I know the coach back at UT.
And they don't usually send reps
to Silver Falls,
but I told them they needed to meet you.
What?
Thank you, Coach.
Yeah. Hey, you… you deserved it.
And the rep had a ton to say about you.
-He loved you.
-[chuckles]
He said he's gonna do his best
come admission-decision time.
Thank you, Coach. I…
If I get in, um, um, I won't let you down.
No, when you get in.
All right, let's go. I got an announcement
I gotta make to the team.
Whoa. You don't…
you don't have to tell them.
If only that was it.
What?
All right, team. Put your shirts back on.
Thought we had practice.
[coach] Unfortunately,
the Lockwood soccer team
snuck into the weed shop with fake IDs
and got higher
than the fireworks on the 4th of July.
So now every team in the area
has to take a drug test.
[boys groan]
But, no, don't worry.
It's just standard. It's all very fair.
Even Coach Walter has to take one too.
Okay, you two. Let's go. You're up.
Dude, there's no way I'm gonna pass.
I smoked that joint at the rodeo.
If you test positive,
you'll miss a couple games.
You wanna tell my dad that?
No, I… I… I guess not.
Okay, um…
But you haven't been smoking, right?
-No.
-Okay, so you can take the test for me.
What?
We can sneak some of your sample
and use it as mine.
Coach Allen probably lends you
his office keys all the time.
-We'd get caught.
-No, we wouldn't.
Man, I need this.
You think college reps would consider me
after I failed a drug test?
Cole, I'd do the same for you.
[suspenseful music playing]
Downloaded From MoviesMod.Org